

EDUCATION

Basic Certificate Course (BCC)

Wisdom International Leadership Institute, (WILI) 2018.

Senior Secondary School Certificate Examination (SSCE) Community Senior Secondary School, 2017.

CONTACT

PHONE

(+234) 906-7460-198

EMAIL

Christianlightgentry@gmail.com

WEBSITE

https://xtianmedia.netlify.app

ADDRESS

Agip Estate, Mile 4, Rumueme,
Port Harcourt, Nigeria.

REFERENCE

Will be made available on request.

CHRISTIAN EZE

DIGITAL MEDIA SPECIALIST

ABOUT ME

A proficient and dexterous digital media specialist based in Port-Harcourt, Nigeria.

He is the creative director of xtianmedia, a brand that incorporates all his skills and expertise.

He specializes on Creative Video Editing, Live Video Streaming/Virtual Set Up, Graphic designs, Web Designs and Social media management.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2018 - Present Live Video Streamer

Wisdom Power Christian Centre

In- charge of broadcasting online live videos & prerecorded, with well relatable software.

2020 - Present Media Manager

Wisdom Power Christian Centre

Strategize media workflow with the eye to see through media processes making sure there's no technical

disruption

2019 - Present Creative Director

Xtianmedia

Designed flyers, logos, banners using a well-defined

Info graphics.

Edit videos and motion graphics suitable for brand

voices.

SOFT SKILLS

He is a life-long learner with great communication skills, a team player and a problem solver, highly proficient in time management skills with an eminent attitude for results.

SOFTWARE SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop - Adobe Premiere Pro - Adobe illustrator

Microsoft Word - Microsoft PowerPoint - Adobe illustrator

OBS Studio - Vmix